# Satyam sinha

Contact: 8158914106 Website: <a href="https://satyamsinha.com">https://satyamsinha.com</a>

Email: satyamsinha8158@gmail.com

**Location:** Rishra (Hoogly) **Experience**: 2yrs

Current ctc: 3.8 lpa Notice period: 3 months



### **ABOUT ME**

A software proffesional dedicated towards my job and have a target to learn as much as possible and stay updated with the latest technology trends. I carry a 2 year experience in javascript on building frontend sides of the application and some backend part also. My expections are to learn more about technology like React, Angular, Nodejs backend and database stuffs also.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## 1. COLORBRACKET TECHNOLOGY LLP (2021-2022)

I worked here as a Javascript developer.

Products I worked on:

Zapster delivery ecosystem, Echol ERP, JSON UI Builder, URA and Mantro ERP

## 2. NAVIGATORS SOFTWARES PVT. LTD. (2022-Present)

I am working here as a software developer.

Product I am working on is responsible for insurance and policy related stuff based on US Client.

#### **EDUCATION**

## 1. SAINT THOMAS HIGH SCHOOL (- 2013)

Passed madhyamik with 7.4 CGPA

### 2. SAINT JOSEPH HIGH SCHOOL (2013-2015)

Passed higher secondary with 58%

## 3. BC COLLEGE (2015-2018)

Dropped math honours in last year.

## 4. ABS Academy (2019-2022)

BCA - 9.0

# Satyam sinha

Contact: 8158914106 Website: <a href="https://satyamsinha.com">https://satyamsinha.com</a>

Email: satyamsinha8158@gmail.com

**Location:** Rishra (Hoogly) **Experience**: 2yrs

Current ctc: 3.8 lpa Notice period: 3 months



### **ABOUT ME**

A software proffesional dedicated towards my job and have a target to learn as much as possible and stay updated with the latest technology trends. I carry a 2 year experience in javascript on building frontend sides of the application and some backend part also. My expections are to learn more about technology like React, Angular, Nodejs backend and database stuffs also.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## 1. COLORBRACKET TECHNOLOGY LLP (2021-2022)

I worked here as a Javascript developer.

Products I worked on:

Zapster delivery ecosystem, Echol ERP, JSON UI Builder, URA and Mantro ERP

## 2. NAVIGATORS SOFTWARES PVT. LTD. (2022-Present)

I am working here as a software developer.

Product I am working on is responsible for insurance and policy related stuff based on US Client.

#### **EDUCATION**

## 1. SAINT THOMAS HIGH SCHOOL (- 2013)

Passed madhyamik with 7.4 CGPA

### 2. SAINT JOSEPH HIGH SCHOOL (2013-2015)

Passed higher secondary with 58%

## 3. BC COLLEGE (2015-2018)

Dropped math honours in last year.

## 4. ABS Academy (2019-2022)

BCA - 9.0